Hey guys, welcome back.
I hope you have actually gone
through the Agent AI course I asked you
to do before coming here.
That is very, very important
because that course already talks about how
to pull data, this exact data.
Okay? So I'll be sharing this code that is written
with the help of the ai, with the help
of Amazon Q, in fact, okay?
I'll share this quote to you, and this is a Python script
and this you will use in the glue python shell.
To know more about glue, python glue, go to the deep dive
and understand what glue is all about.
This right here, you'll do just the hands-on part.
See, my intention for you is that you don't feel
that coding is your Achilles heel anymore, okay?
And if you have truly gone through my agent, take AI course
and and truly done the hands-on, not just watched it, okay?
If you have really done the hands-on, I'm pretty sure
by now you would've felt that I
don't have to worry about coding at all.
So the next few videos are all gonna be out, hands-on.
Make sure you follow along and get the hands-on done. Okay?
Talk to you soon.